let's create this crocodile with simple
让我们用简单的方法创建这条鳄鱼
shapes
形状
I drew this crocodile in I will
我把这条鳄鱼画进了我的意志
import this drawing in inkscape and
在Inkscape中导入此绘图，然后
vectorize it I go to file import
将其矢量化我转到文件导入
I select the sketch and click on open
我选择草图并点击打开
I click on OK I want to resize the
我单击确定，我想要调整
canvas to match the size of my drawing
画布要与我的绘画大小相匹配
to do this I right click and click on
为此，我右键单击，然后单击
document properties
文档属性
then I click on the resize to content
然后，我点击调整到内容的大小
icon
图标
I zoom in by pressing Ctrl and scrolling
我通过按Ctrl键并滚动来放大
forward and I can pan by pressing the
向前，我可以通过按下
middle Mouse button and drag to be able
鼠标中键并拖动即可启用
to see both the drawing and the artwork
同时查看图纸和图稿的步骤
I will create a new layer I click on the
我将创建一个新层，然后单击
add layer icon and click on ADD
Add Layer图标并点击Add
I will place the layer below the layer
我将把层放在层的下面
with the drawing by clicking on the move
通过单击移动来使用图形
down in the stack icon I hold my mouse
在堆栈图标中，我拿着鼠标
above layer 1 and click on the Square
在Layer 1上方并单击正方形
icon I set the layer to multiply so I
图标我将层设置为正片，这样我
can see the layer below and I can look
我可以看到下面的那一层，我可以看
through the drawing
通过绘图
I will also set its opacity to about 15
我还会将其不透明度设置为约15
and I will lock the layer so the drawing
我将锁定该层，以便绘制
can't be moved I will start by drawing
我不能移动，我将从画开始
the eyes which are made of circles I
由圆圈组成的眼睛是
will create them with the ellipse tool I
将使用椭圆工具i创建它们
zoom in on the left eye I drag and also
放大我拖动的左眼，同时
hold down the control key so I get a
按住Ctrl键，这样我就可以
perfect circle
完美圆
each shape you draw can have a fill in a
您绘制的每个形状都可以在
stroke to give the circle a fill color I
描边以使圆具有填充颜色
can click on a color in the swatches
可以点击样本中的一种颜色
panel and to give the circle a stroke
面板，并给圆圈一个笔划
color you shift-click on a color notice
按住Shift键并单击颜色通知的颜色
the used fill color swatch has a dot in
已使用的填充颜色样本中有一个圆点
it and the stroke color swatch is
它和笔划颜色样本是
indicated with a larger circle line
用较大的圆线表示
so how do I remove the stroke I remove
那么，如何删除我删除的笔划呢
The Stroke by shift-clicking on the Red
按住Shift键并单击红色的笔划
Cross the Red Cross now shows the circle
红十字现在显示了圆圈
line
线
I also want a slightly different green
我也想要略微不同的绿色
for my fill
对我来说很充实
although the dot and circle line make it
尽管圆点和圆线构成了
easy to find back the used colors I
很容易找到我用过的颜色
would like to have the used colors at
我想把用过的颜色放在
the top for easy access to do this I
为了便于访问，顶部是
right click on the Swatch and choose pin
在样例上单击鼠标右键并选择别针
color
颜色
now let's finish the eye
现在让我们来完成这只眼睛
with the ellipse tool I can make the
使用椭圆工具，我可以使
circle larger but I prefer to do this
圆圈更大，但我更喜欢这样做
with the select tool because then I can
选择工具，因为这样我就可以
drag from every corner
从每个角落拖动
so I drag a corner while holding down
所以我在按住的同时拖了一个角
control to keep the circle round
控件使圆保持圆形。
now I press Ctrl D to duplicate the
现在我按Ctrl D复制
circle the duplicate is placed exactly
圆圈复制品被准确地放置
on top of the original
在原始的基础上
I make the copy white by clicking on the
我通过点击下面的
white Swatch now I will make the eye
白色的斯沃琪现在我要做眼睛
smaller to scale the circle from the
较小，以从
center I hold Ctrl shift press down
居中按住Ctrl Shift键并按下
while dragging although the pupil is
在拖拽时，虽然瞳孔是
black to see what I am doing I will
黑色，看看我在做什么，我会
temporarily choose Gray
临时选择灰色
the pupil is not round so now I will
这个学生不是圆的，所以现在我要圆了
drag from the sides to make the
从两侧拖动以使
reflection I will duplicate the white
反射我将复制白色
circle I hold Ctrl and drag it in place
圆圈我按住Ctrl键并将其拖动到位
I will now make the pupil black I press
我现在要把我按下的瞳孔调成黑色
Ctrl and scroll backward to zoom out
按Ctrl键并向后滚动可缩小
let's copy the left eye and reuse it for
让我们复制左眼并重复使用它
the right eye in the layers panel we see
我们在图层面板中看到的右眼
the eye is created with four circles to
眼睛是由四个圆创建的，以
copy them and move them together I will
将它们复制并移动到一起，我会的
make them a group I drag over them to
让他们成为我拖到他们身上的一个组
select them all I right click on the
全部选中。我右键单击
selected items and choose group
所选项目并选择分组
in the layers panel we see we now have a
在Layers面板中，我们现在有一个
group I can open and close the group and
组I可以打开和关闭组并
I can give the group a name by double
我可以用两个字给这个小组起个名字
clicking on it I type left eye we see
点击它，我输入我们看到的左眼
the group behaves as if it is a single
该组的行为就像它是一个
object
对象
so I will press Ctrl D to duplicate the
因此，我将按Ctrl D来复制
group and I will place the copied group
组和我将放置复制的组
over the other eye I will call the new
在另一只眼睛上，我将称为新的
group right eye now I reuse the group
群右眼现在我重新使用群
once again to make the nostrils I press
再一次让我按下鼻孔
Ctrl D once again to duplicate the group
再次按Ctrl D复制该组
the nostrils don't need the pupils and
鼻孔不需要瞳孔和
highlight so I can remove these to do
突出显示，以便我可以删除这些要执行的操作
this I will ungroup the group
这一次，我将解组
I click on the highlight and press
我点击突出显示并按下
delete and I also delete the pupil
删除，我也删除了这个瞳孔
the nostrils like the scutes are brown
像盾牌一样的鼻孔是棕色的
so I click on the white circle and in my
所以我点击白色圆圈，在我的
swatches I choose a brown
我选的是棕色的
I right click on the Swatch and choose
我用鼠标右键单击色板并选择
pin color now I select the two circles
大头针颜色现在我选择两个圆圈
right click and choose group I will
右键单击并选择组I Will
scale the nostril down and place it
把鼻孔缩小，然后放在
I press Ctrl D and position the other
我按下Ctrl D键并定位另一个
nostril
鼻孔
I hold shift and click on the other
我按住Shift键并单击另一个键
nostril to select them both I right
鼻孔都选好了，我对了
click and choose group I now have two
单击并选择组我现在有两个
groups placed in a new group I will call
放置在新组中的组我将称为
the group nostrils for the belly I drag
群鼻孔为我拖着肚子
another ellipse I click on a yellow
另一个省略号，我点击黄色
Swatch I right click on the Swatch and
我在色板上单击鼠标右键并
choose pin color finally I make the
选择大头针的颜色最后我做了
mouth with the ellipse tool to use the
用椭圆工具来使用口部
ellipse tool for scaling drag one of the
用于缩放的椭圆工具拖动其中一个
two squares and to move the circle drag
两个方块和移动的圆圈拖动
the cross in the middle until now we
中间的十字架直到现在我们
have only used fill colors for our
仅对我们的
circles in the swatches panel I can see
我可以看到色板面板中的圆圈
that my circle has no stroke
我的圆圈没有中风
to add a stroke I shift-click on a
若要添加笔划，请按住Shift并单击
Swatch I need the stroke to be the same
斯沃琪我需要的是相同的划水
width as the mouth I click on the fill
宽度作为我点击的填充物
and stroke Tab and then on stroke style
和笔划选项卡，然后打开笔划样式
a width of 0.5 millimeter looks right to
0.5毫米的宽度看起来正好
remove the fill color I click on the Red
删除我单击的红色的填充颜色
Cross now the circle only has a stroke
现在交叉，圆圈只有一划
with the ellipse tool I can drag the
使用椭圆工具，我可以将
little circle at the right in two ways
右边的小圆圈有两个方向
if I drag and hold my mouse outside of
如果我将鼠标拖动并按住在
the circle I can create pie charts and
圆圈我可以创建饼图和
when I drag while holding my mouse
当我按住鼠标拖动时
inside the circle I can create Arc lines
在圆内，我可以创建圆弧线
behind cap I choose round cap so that
在帽子后面，我选择了圆帽，这样
the line will be rounded at the edges I
这条线的边缘将是圆角的
shift-click on the black Swatch to make
按住Shift键并单击黑色色板以制作
the stroke black
黑色的笔划
in the next lecture we will look at the
在下一节课中，我们将了解
rectangle tool
矩形工具
foreign
国外